<?xml version='1.0' ?><rss version='2.0'><channel><title>SMI Project 37</title><description>Travel Guide</description><language>en-UK</language><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php</link><item><title>Pyramids</title><description>The Great Pyramid of Giza (also known as the Pyramid of Khufu or the Pyramid of Cheops) is the oldest and largest of the three pyramids in the Giza pyramid complex bordering present-day Giza in Greater Cairo, Egypt. It is the oldest of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World, and the only one to remain largely intact.</description><comments>Ainda sem nada aqui</comments><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php/article.php?type=view&amp;id=13</link></item><item><title>Japan</title><description>Japan is an island country in East Asia. Located in the northwest Pacific Ocean, it borders the Sea of Japan to the west, and stretches from the Sea of Okhotsk in the north to the East China Sea and Taiwan in the south.</description><comments>Ainda sem nada aqui</comments><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php/article.php?type=view&amp;id=15</link></item><item><title>Brazil</title><description>Brazil officially the Federative Republic of Brazil (Portuguese: República Federativa do Brasil, About this soundlisten is the largest country in both South America and Latin America. At 8.5 million square kilometers (3.2 million square miles)[11] and with over 211 million people, Brazil is the world&#39;s fifth-largest country by area and the sixth most populous.</description><comments>Ainda sem nada aqui</comments><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php/article.php?type=view&amp;id=20</link></item><item><title>Germany</title><description>Germany, officially the Federal Republic of Germany is a country in Central and Western Europe. Covering an area of 357,022 square kilometres (137,847 sq mi), it lies between the Baltic and North seas to the north, and the Alps to the south. It borders Denmark to the north, Poland and the Czech Republic to the east, Austria and Switzerland to the south, and France, Luxembourg, Belgium, and the Netherlands to the west.</description><comments>Ainda sem nada aqui</comments><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php/article.php?type=view&amp;id=21</link></item><item><title>Spain</title><description>Spain , officially the Kingdom of Spain is a country in Southwestern Europe with some pockets of territory across the Strait of Gibraltar and the Atlantic Ocean.[12] Its continental European territory is situated on the Iberian Peninsula. Its territory also includes two archipelagoes: the Canary Islands off the coast of Africa, and the Balearic Islands in the Mediterranean Sea.</description><comments>Ainda sem nada aqui</comments><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php/article.php?type=view&amp;id=22</link></item><item><title>African Burial Ground</title><description>Re-discovered in 1991 during excavations for a new federal building, this former burial ground that contains the remains of more than 400 free and enslaved Africans buried during the 17th and 18th centuries was designated a National Historic Landmark memorial in 1993.</description><comments>Ainda sem nada aqui</comments><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php/article.php?type=view&amp;id=23</link></item><item><title>Little Bighorn Battlefield</title><description>The 1876 Battle of the Little Bighorn between George Armstrong Custer&#39;s 7th Cavalry and a combined Lakota Sioux, Northern Cheyenne and Arapaho force led by Sitting Bull and Crazy Horse took place here.</description><comments>Ainda sem nada aqui</comments><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php/article.php?type=view&amp;id=24</link></item><item><title>Mount St. Helens</title><description>Following the 1980 eruption of the now-8,363-foot-tall (2,549 m) Mount St. Helens, the environment was left to respond naturally to the disturbance. The volcanic crater is surrounded by a pumice plain with deposits from the landslide, preserved wind-blown trees, and the Ape Cave lava tube.[</description><comments>Ainda sem nada aqui</comments><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php/article.php?type=view&amp;id=25</link></item><item><title>Sydney Opera House</title><description>The Sydney Opera House is a multi-venue performing arts centre at Sydney Harbour in Sydney, New South Wales, Australia. It is one of the 20th century&#39;s most famous and distinctive buildings.

Designed by Danish architect Jørn Utzon, but completed by an Australian architectural team headed up by Peter Hall, the building was formally opened on 20 October 1973 after a gestation beginning with Utzon&#39;s 1957 selection as winner of an international design competition. The Government of New South Wales, led by the premier, Joseph Cahill, authorised work to begin in 1958 with Utzon directing construction. The government&#39;s decision to build Utzon&#39;s design is often overshadowed by circumstances that followed, including cost and scheduling overruns as well as the architect&#39;s ultimate resignation.</description><comments>Ainda sem nada aqui</comments><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php/article.php?type=view&amp;id=26</link></item><item><title>London</title><description>London is the capital and largest city of England and the United Kingdom. Standing on the River Thames in the south-east of England, at the head of its 50-mile (80 km) estuary leading to the North Sea, London has been a major settlement for two millennia. Londinium was founded by the Romans. The City of London, London&#39;s ancient core − an area of just 1.12 square miles (2.9 km2) and colloquially known as the Square Mile − retains boundaries that closely follow its medieval limits. The City of Westminster is also an Inner London borough holding city status. London is governed by the Mayor of London and the London Assembly.</description><comments>Ainda sem nada aqui</comments><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php/article.php?type=view&amp;id=27</link></item><item><title>South Africa</title><description>South Africa, officially the Republic of South Africa (RSA), is the southernmost country in Africa. With over 58 million people, it is the world&#39;s 24th-most populous nation and covers an area of 1,221,037 square kilometres (471,445 sq mi). South Africa has three designated capital cities: executive Pretoria, judicial Bloemfontein and legislative Cape Town. The largest city is Johannesburg. About 80% of South Africans are of Bantu ancestry, divided among a variety of ethnic groups speaking different African languages.[10] The remaining population consists of Africa&#39;s largest communities of European, Asian, Indian, and multiracial ancestry.</description><comments>Ainda sem nada aqui</comments><link>http://localhost/smi/g37/RSS.php/article.php?type=view&amp;id=28</link></item></channel></rss>